fashiongrosir.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Fashion Grosir dot com

### Categories

### Sale Sale Sale

  * Fashion Obral

### House Brand

  * William
  * VXY
  * Koleksi Sprei
  * New You

### Customer Service

### Catalog Subscription

EMAIL Catalog? Type your email

### Status Order

### Testimony

Jika Anda puas, beritahu pada teman dan kerabat Anda. Jika Anda tidak puas, beritahu kami.  
klik untuk email  
  
---  
  
Dear FasGro,

Barang2 pesenanku udah nyampai semua ke semarang, saluuuutttt deh buat fasgro, senin baru transfer, selasa siang udah nyampe ke smg sampai tercengang ak... Pokoknya barang bagus, bungkusannya rapi, service memuaskan.

Sukses selalu yah!!!

Regards,

_ASTI - Semarang_

BaJu nya OkeY ..   
Pelayanan nya cePat !!!   
Thanks Fashion grosir .. smoga ada barang2 sale lagiiiii ....

_Jessie, Bandung_

Testimonial Lainnya  
  
> ### -Collection and Use of Information-
> 
>   
>  When you place your order, you will be asked to provide basic information such as your name, postal address, email address and other personally identifiable information. Refusal to supply these information may result in us being unable to process your request order.
> 
> We take your privacy very seriously and our goal is to protect your information. We will at all times try to ensure that the personal information you give us is kept appropriately secure and processed fairly and lawfully. 
> 
> ### -Disclosure of Information-
> 
>   
>  FashionGrosir fully respects your privacy. Your information will be kept confidential. Please be assured that any information that you provide, such as your e-mail or postal address, etc is for our own internal use only or to enable us to respond to your order and feedback. 
> 
> ### -Question You Might Ask-
> 
>   
>  Why do you need to collect my personal information? 
> 
> When you place an order with us we collect certain personal information from you, for example, your name, postal address, phone numbers, e-mail addresses and credit/debit card numbers. We use this information to identify you as a customer, to process your order to deliver products, to process payments and to update our records. We also use this information to generally manage your account with us and to provide you with information about our products. We will also collect personal information from you at other times, such as if you register to receive email updates and new arrival updates from us (even if you do not place an order with us). This will be used to provide you with information about our products. 
> 
> Do you give my personal information to other third parties? 
> 
> Where you have consented to our doing so we do not share the information you have provided with any other third party.
